A Finding Aid to the William P. Daley Papers, 1905-2004 (bulk 1951-2001), in the Archives of American Art AAA.dalewill
Archives of American Art
William P. Daley papers
bulk 1951-2001
1905-2004
AAA.dalewill
Archives of American Art
15.2 Linear feet
The papers of ceramist William P. Daley measure 15.2 linear feet and date from 1905-2004 (bulk 1951-2001). The collection documents Daley's career as both artist and teacher through biographical information, correspondence, exhibition files, project files, material on workshops, seminars, and lectures, teaching files, artist files, reference files, printed material, photographs, financial files, and artwork.
William P. Daley
Biographical Note
Born in Hastings-on-Hudson, New York, in 1925, William P. Daley developed an interest in art at an early age, and was encouraged by his parents William and Alice. In 1943 Daley finished high school and enlisted in the Army Air Corps. When the war ended, he returned home, and with the help of the G.I. Bill, completed a B.S. in Art Education from Massachusetts College of Art, and a M.A. from the Teachers College at Columbia University. While at the Massachusetts College of Art he met and married fellow student Catherine Stennes. They had three children together, Barbara, Charlotte, and Thomas.
Originally intending to focus on painting, Daley discovered his love for ceramics while in art school. Much of his early work after graduation consisted of architectural and sculptural commissions. From 1961 to 1965 he held teaching positions as a ceramics instructor at the University of Northern Iowa, State University of New York at New Paltz, Philadelphia College of Art and Design, and the State University of New York at Fredonia. In 1965 he settled in Elkins Park, Pennsylvania and returned to the Philadelphia College of Art and Design, University of the Arts. There he taught in both the Industrial Design and Craft Department until his retirement from the college in 1990. When not teaching in the classroom, and even after retirement, Daley traveled extensively giving workshops and lectures at art centers, high schools, colleges, and universities. He has won several awards for teaching in the arts, including the College Art Association of America Distinguished Teaching of Art Award in 1991.
Daley became an active member of the crafts movement in Philadelphia, co-founding the Philadelphia Council of Professional Craftsmen. The Helen Drutt Gallery opened in Philadelphia in 1974 and gave Daley his first one man show there. Later, the gallery would become Daley's primary dealer. A self-proclaimed "mud man" and maker of "cosmic pots," Daley has focused throughout his career on the issues of the ceramic vessel, using drawings to explore his ideas. In 1994 the Renwick Gallery held a retrospective entitled, "William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings" which featured thirty years of his work. William Daley is still producing new work today.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of ceramist William Daley measure 15.2 linear feet and date from 1905-2004 (bulk 1951-2001). The collection documents Daley's career as both artist and teacher through biographical information, correspondence, exhibition files, project files, material on workshops, seminars, and lectures, teaching files, artist files, reference files, printed material, photographs, financial files, and artwork.
Biographical files encompass items from Daley's early life including family, education, and military materials, as well as files on awards he has earned, and interviews he has given during his career. Correspondence includes general correspondence with family, friends, artists, colleagues, and schools, as well as named files on correspondence with galleries, organizations, and individuals. The largest series in the collection, Exhibition Files, spanning a fifty year period, contain materials on group and solo exhibitions in which Daley participated, and also includes Auction Files and Exhibition Juror Files. Project Files contain materials related to public and private commissions.
Workshops, Seminars, and Lectures, documents the numerous events at which Daley taught or spoke on topics of art, ceramics, and/or education. Many of these topics are also found in Writings, which include drafts of writings by Daley and others. Within this series Daley's personal address lists and calendars are also found. The Teaching Files provide insight into Daley's teaching methods, primarily at the Philadelphia College of Art, from materials such as curriculum plans, lesson notes, and assignments. Also within this series are general teaching notes which contain many hand drawn diagrams. The Artist Files that Daley created house materials concerning artists who were friends, former students, co-workers, and colleagues. Daley also compiled Reference Files containing materials on various topics for use in teaching and projects. Topics include the art of various countries, formulas and tables for ceramics, essays on art and education, and other general subjects. Printed Material provides information, primarily on ceramics, through press clippings, exhibit announcements, catalogs and journals, as well as other miscellaneous materials. Also found are reviews of Daley's work. While photographs are included throughout the collection, the Photographs series contains additional photographs of Daley in the studio or in the classroom, as well as photographs of artwork by others. Also found in the collection are copies of drawings Daley completed throughout his career.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into thirteen series. Each series is arranged either in rough chronological or alphabetical order.
Series 1: Biographical Files, 1905-2003 (Box 1; 0.5 linear feet)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1957-2001, undated (Boxes 1-2; 1.5 linear feet)
Series 3: Exhibition Files, 1949-1999, undated (Boxes 3-5; 2.7 linear feet)
Series 4: Project Files, 1956-2000 (Boxes 5-6; 1.0 linear foot)
Series 5: Workshops, Seminars, and Lectures, 1958-1998, undated, (Boxes 6-8; 2.3 linear feet)
Series 6: Writings, 1951-2003, undated (Box 9; 0.6 linear feet)
Series 7: Teaching Files, 1951-1998, undated (Boxes 9-10; 1.3 linear feet)
Series 8: Artist Files, 1938-2001, undated (Boxes 10-12; 2.1 linear feet)
Series 9: Reference Files, 1951-2001, undated (Box 13; 1.0 linear foot)
Series 10: Printed Material, 1936-2004 (Boxes 14-15; 1.9 linear feet)
Series 11: Photographs, 1953-2001, undated (Box 15; 5 folders)
Series 12: Financial Files, 1962-1997, undated (Box 16; 4 folders)
Series 13: Artwork, 1954-2003, undated (Boxes 15-16; 3 folders)
Provenance
The William P. Daley papers were donated by Daley in 2003.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment and is limited to the Washington, D.C. research facility.
Chihuly, Dale, 1941-; Howard, Robert Boardman, 1896-1983; Nanette L. Laitman Documentation Project for Craft and Decorative Arts in America; Philadelphia College of Art. -- Faculty; Schreckengost, Viktor, 1906-; Art--Study and teaching; Ceramicists; Drawings; Glazes--Formulae; Interviews; Photographs; Potters; Pottery--Study and teaching--Pennsylvania; Pottery--Technique; Sculptors--Pennsylvania; Transcripts
- Biographical Files, 1905-2003, undated; Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet Box 1
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes artist statements, a brief biography and professional history of Daley, as well as school and military records. It also contains files on William Daley's Honorary Doctorates and numerous other awards and typically include correspondence, brochures, and other related materials concerning the awards. Also found are documents associated with Daley's family, including correspondence with his parents during World War II and materials on his father, William Joseph Daley. There are files on two oral history interviews including a 120 page interview of Daley conducted in 1985 by the Columbia University American Craftspeople Oral History Project. This series is arranged alphabetically by type of material and chronologically under each heading. Most materials prior to 1950 are photocopies.
  - Artist Statements, 1956, 1997, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Awards, National Council on Education for the Ceramic Arts Honorary Membership, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Awards, State University of New York Research Foundation Grant-In-Aid Award, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Awards, American Institute of Architects Craftsmanship Medal Award Nomination, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Awards, National Endowment for the Arts Craftsmen's Fellowship Grant, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Awards, Massachusetts College of Art Outstanding Achievement Award, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Awards, Philadelphia College of Art Venture Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Awards, American Craft Council's College of Fellows, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Awards, University of the Arts, University Professor of the Arts, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Awards, College Art Association Distinguished Teaching of Art Award, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
  - Awards, Art Matters' Lifetime Achievement Award, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Awards, PEW Fellowship Nomination, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards, Interior Design Council's Roland A. Gallimore Memorial Award, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Awards, Massachusetts College of Art Distinguished Alumnus 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Awards, American Craft Council Aileen Osborn Webb 2003 Gold Medal (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Biography/Professional History, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Birth and Baptismal Certificates, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Education, School Records, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Education, High School Artwork, 1942, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Education, Letters of Recommendation, 1943, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Education, Massachusetts School of Art Records, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Education, Acceptance Letter from Radcliffe College, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Education, Teachers College, Columbia University Records, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Family, William Joseph Daley Materials, 1905, 1919, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Family, Correspondence with Parents During War, 1944, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Maine College of Art, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Philadelphia College of Art and Design, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Interview, Fine Arts Brochure, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Interview, Columbia University American Craftspeople Oral History Project, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Military, Service Records, 1943-1950, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Military, Veterans Administration Records, 1945-1951 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Correspondence, 1957-2001, undated; Series 2; 1.5 Linear feet Boxes 1-2
  This series contains both personal and professional correspondence. A significant amount of correspondence related to William Daley's professional career is also located within series 3, 4, and 5, and correspondence with certain artists is found in the Artist Files in Series 8.
  Arrangement note
  The Correspondence Files are arranged into two subseries:
  2.1: General Correspondence, 1957-2001, undated
  2.2: Named Files, 1959-2000, undated
  - General Correspondence, 1957-2001, undated; 2.1
    General Correspondence primarily consists of letters of a more personal nature from family, friends, artists, and colleagues, including numerous cards and postcards. Also within are requests from galleries, schools, universities, and art associations for Daley to take part in exhibitions or workshops. Files are arranged chronologically by year.
    - General Correspondence, 1957-1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 33-51)
    - General Correspondence, 1986-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1-27)
  - Named Files, 1959-2000, undated; 2.2
    Named Files are arranged alphabetically by the correspondents name and contain primarily professional correspondence to and from Daley. Included are files on galleries, such as Exhibit A and Garth Clark Gallery, and several councils and organizations in which Daley was a member. There are also files on individuals with whom Daley exchanged a significant amount of correspondence over a long period of time. Most notable is Helen Drutt, owner of the Helen Drutt Gallery which represents Daley's artwork.
    - American Crafts Council, 1976-1979, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Art Advisory Council, Wills Eye Hospital, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Bates, Wayne, 1979-1982, 1990-1998, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Braunstein Gallery, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Bryant, Keith, 1987-1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Busch, Gail, 1982-1995, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Ceramics Monthly, 1979-1980, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Colburn, Anthony, 1990-1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Drutt, Helen, 1979-2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Exhibit A, 1977-1985, undated (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
    - Garth Clark Gallery, 1978-1991, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Larsen, Jack Lenor, 1982-1994, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Levin, Elaine, 1979-1990, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Martha Schneider Gallery, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Nelson, Glenn C., 1959, 1968-1984, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - New York State College of Ceramics, 1965, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Philadelphia Council of Professional Craftsmen, 1966, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - The Renzetti Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Wolf, Howard A., 1978-1987, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Exhibition Files, 1949-1999, undated; Series 3; 2.7 Linear feet Boxes 3-5
  The Exhibition Files are organized into three subseries:
  3.1: Exhibition Files, 1949-1998, undated
  3.2: Auction Files, 1979-1993, undated
  3.3: Exhibition Juror Files, 1968-1999
  - Exhibition Files, 1949-1998, undated; 3.1
    Exhibition Files contain material on the numerous group and solo exhibits in which William Daley participated. Files typically include correspondence, expense lists and receipts, price lists, and printed materials, including brochures, catalogs, announcements, and press clippings. A few files also contain photographs. Files are arranged chronologically by year of exhibition.
    - New England Painting and Sculpture (1949) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Decorative Arts and Ceramics Exhibition, 1949, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - "Craftsmen of the Midwestern College Art Conference" (1952) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Iowa Artists Show, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Blackhawk County Art Show, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Iowa State Teachers College Invitational (1953) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Fiber, Clay, Metal 1953 Craft Competition (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - American Craftsman's Educational Council, Young Americans 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - American Craftsman's Educational Council, Young Americans 1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - New York Society of Ceramic Arts 61st Annual Exhibition (1955) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - New Paltz Craft Cooperative Shop (1956) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Fifth Annual Miami National Ceramic Exhibition (1957) (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Pace Gallery, circa 1959 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia Art Alliance 46th Season (1960) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Everson Museum of Art 22nd Ceramic National (1962) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Scripps College Twentieth Annual Invitational Ceramic Exhibition (1964) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sculpture, Ceramics, Drawings: Old Main Gallery (1965) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Gallery 1015 (1966), 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Penn State Exhibition (1966) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 24th Ceramic National (1966) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Craftsmen '67, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - First Survey of Contemporary American Crafts, University of Texas (1967), 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Ceramic Design, Philadelphia Art Alliance (1967), 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 25th Ceramic National, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Fourth National Invitational Craft Exhibition (1968) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Artists Equity Exhibition (1968) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - "Ceramics by William Daley" (1969), 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Drawing Exhibition at Beaver College (1969) (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Craftsmen '70, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - CRAFTS 1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Craftsmen '73, circa 1973 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University of New Mexico Invitational Craft Exhibition, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - William Daley at Helen Drutt Gallery (1974) (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Clay U.S.A. (1975), 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - "Philadelphia: Three Centuries of American Art" (1976), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Exhibition of Liturgical Arts (1976) (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - William Daley at the Helen Drutt Gallery (1976) (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Soup Tureens: 1976 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Contemporary Clay: Ten Approaches (1976), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Millersville State College 5th Annual Clay Invitational (1977) (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - The Philadelphia Craft Show (1977) (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Vessel as Metaphor (1977) (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Art in Service of Liturgy (1978) (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Artists Equity Triennial Exhibition (1978) (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Century of Ceramics in the United States 1878-1978, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 45-46)
    - "Wayne Bates, William Daley, Richard Reinhardt" (1978), 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - "William P. Daley: Ceramic Sculpture at Braunstein Gallery" (1979), 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Central Iowa Art Association Ceramic Study Collection, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Fiber, Clay, & Metal (1979) (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - "Invitational Clay/Fiber/Metal Exhibition" (1979) (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Olaf Skoogfors: 20th Century Goldsmith (1979) (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - The Contemporary American Potter (1980), 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 53-54)
    - Philadelphia: Clay 1980, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Contemporary Ceramics: A Response to Wedgewood (1980), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - William P. Daley Ceramics at Helen Drutt Gallery (1980) (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Celebrate Haystack, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - American Potters I and II (1981) (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - William Daley: Recent Works at Exhibit A (1981) (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Skidmore College Fifth National Crafts Invitational (1981) (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - East Coast Vessels, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Who's Afraid of American Pottery? (1983), 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 63-64)
    - William Daley at the Massachusetts College of Art (1982) (Box 3, Folder 65-66)
    - Philadelphia College of Art: Inside/Outside (1982) (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Mankato State University Invitational, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - "Art in Craft Media" (1983) (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - New Works in Clay by William Daley, Elsa Rady, Betty Woodman, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Affects/Effects 2 (1983) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - American Clay Artists: Philadelphia '83, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Ceramic Echoes: Historical References in Contemporary Ceramics (1983) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - William P. Daley at the Helen Drutt Gallery (1983) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Works on Paper (1983) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Clay in New Mexico '83, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "A Salute to Pennsylvania's Artistic Heritage" (1983) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "Skidmore Craft Invitational '84", 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Clay Vessels (1984) (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - U.S. News and World Report (1984) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - "Continental Insurance 1984: The Continental Collection" (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - William Daley at Alfred University (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Bill Daley at Garth Clark Gallery (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Pottery Questions II (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Ceramists: The Container (1984), 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - William Daley Vessels at Braunstein Gallery (1985), 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Architectural Clay/Clay in Architecture (1985) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - "Big Containment" (1986), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Contemporary Arts: An Expanding View (1986), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "Contemporary Crafts: A Concept in Flux" (1986) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - 27th Ceramic National Exhibition (1987), 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "Contemporary American Ceramics" (1987), 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Investigations of the Mind (1987) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - "Ceramic Artists: Works on Paper" (1987) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Craft Today: Poetry of the Physical (1987-1988) (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Craft Today: USA (1988-1992), 1986-1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - William Daley at Garth Clark Gallery (1988), 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - New Art Forms (1988) (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - William Daley at Helen Drutt Gallery (1988), 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - "Oval Chamber" at the Renwick Gallery (1988), 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - American Clay Artists 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Clay/Fiber/Metal Invitational 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Contemporary Artifacts 1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - "Faculty Drawing Exhibition at the University of the Arts" (1989) (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - "Mirror Images" (1989) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - International Ceramics Competition '89, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - William Daley: 1990-1980 (Box 4, Folder 37-39)
    - Montgomery County Artists Invitational Art Show (1990) (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - William Daley at Helen Drutt Gallery (1990) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - "Visiting Artists Program: 20th Year Anniversary Show" (1991), 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Scale/Detail (1991), 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - National Ceramic Invitational at West Chester University (1992), 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - "Impressions Through Plaster" (1992), 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Philadelphia College of Art Exhibition, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - A Decade of Craft: Recent Acquisitions at the American Craft Museum (1992) (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Contemporary Crafts by Pennsylvanian Artists (1992) (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Inside/Outside: Ceramics and Drawings by William Daley (1993), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Contemporary American Ceramics at Stetson University (1993), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - The Year of American Craft (1993), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - UnConventional Art (1993) (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Distinguished Alumni Exhibition at Columbia University (1993) (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Wustum Museum of Fine Arts, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings (1993), 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 55-56)
    - Drawing '94: Explorations, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings at the Renwick Gallery (1994) (Box 4, Folder 58-60)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings at the Arkansas Art Center (1994) (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Working in Other Dimensions: Objects and Drawings II (1994) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Clay Studio 20th Anniversary Celebration Exhibition (1994) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 4th International Ceramics Symposium, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Vessels: Three Views (1995) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - William Daley: Ceramic Works and Drawings (1995) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Influenced by Nature (1995-1996) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Wood Turning Center Exhibition (1997), 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania Treasures I (1998), 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Sculpture Objects and Functional Art at SOFA New York, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Mid-Atlantic Contemporary Tile (1998) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Regis Master Series (1998) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Paper Pots II (1998) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Materials, 1962-1963, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Auction Files, 1979-1993, undated; 3.2